<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Weird</title>
    <link>https://itxweird.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Weird</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>itxweird</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2023 22:21:14 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://itxweird.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>I cloned my teachers voice.</title>
      <link>https://itxweird.github.io/posts/teacher_ai_clone/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2023 22:21:14 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://itxweird.github.io/posts/teacher_ai_clone/</guid>
      <description>I cloned my teachers voice. Some of you may have heard of Retrieval-based Voice Conversion otherwise known as RVC. It&amp;rsquo;s a sweet technology that I have no idea of how it actually works. But hey either way I abused the hell out of it.
To start off with the teacher I chose to clone their voice was my math teacher, I&amp;rsquo;ll refer to his as Mr P or PP (yes that is his initals).</description>
      <content>&lt;h1 id=&#34;i-cloned-my-teachers-voice&#34;&gt;I cloned my teachers voice.&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Some of you may have heard of Retrieval-based Voice Conversion otherwise known as RVC. It&amp;rsquo;s a sweet technology that I have no idea of how it actually works. But hey either way I abused the hell out of it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To start off with the teacher I chose to clone their voice was my math teacher, I&amp;rsquo;ll refer to his as Mr P or PP (yes that is his initals). He&amp;rsquo;s a bright bloke with a very enthusiatic and informative voice. He&amp;rsquo;s know from some of his quotes such as &amp;ldquo;Tri tri tri&amp;rdquo; refering to trigonometry. Other ones include &amp;ldquo;Log log log&amp;rdquo; (Logarithms), his greet of &amp;ldquo;Maaaaaaaaathamaticans&amp;rdquo; and other like the &lt;em&gt;spice scale&lt;/em&gt; of math questions. You see, some questions are just plain and boring, Mr P calls this questions just &amp;ldquo;mild &lt;em&gt;white&lt;/em&gt; spice&amp;rdquo; since he strongly believes there some &amp;lsquo;white&amp;rsquo; person spice and &amp;lsquo;asian&amp;rsquo; spice. He gave us a whole anecdote about how he went to this asian restaurant and didn&amp;rsquo;t know if the waiter was gonna give him mild or spicy even though he ask for spicy, he was going on about how the waiter could assume since he&amp;rsquo;s white he wouldn&amp;rsquo;t be able to handle the heat. Anyways&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mr P records all his lessons, which is convienient for me since it allows me have a large quantity of his voice. Although later on I only needed around 1 hours worth. For my first attempt of recreating Mr P&amp;rsquo;s voice, I tried &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.descript.com/overdub&#34;&gt;Descript&lt;/a&gt;, this worked quite well, despite the fact that on the free teir one word in each sentence is replace with &amp;lsquo;Jibber&amp;rsquo;. So I did some research into other alternatives, websites like &lt;a href=&#34;https://elevenlabs.io/&#34;&gt;ElevenLabs&lt;/a&gt; seemed promising but they were all paid services. I wasn&amp;rsquo;t going to spend money so I could clone my teachers voice. Then I stumbled upon RVC, the tool that I would use for the final result.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There&amp;rsquo;s many ways of using RVC, such as local on your own machine, through Google Colab and other online shells. But none of these were really any good. My machine wasn&amp;rsquo;t that fast and would take hours to create a voice copy, google colab was quite finicky and didn&amp;rsquo;t like me trying to create a voice. So at this point I was out of luck, until randomly on the AIHub discord server I get a ping from the announcements channel talking about &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.kits.ai/&#34;&gt;kits.ai&lt;/a&gt;, the announcement said that the website uses RVC which was amazing. I got to work, and in 3 hours I had my voice model. You may think this is where this ends, but silly me didn&amp;rsquo;t really that RVC isn&amp;rsquo;t a straight voice clone, it needs a sample of speech to manipulate in order to make it sound like the voice I had cloned. This was another bummer.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For the next two weeks I spent ages finding a good TTS service that would be able to help me clone Mr. P&amp;rsquo;s voice. I couldn&amp;rsquo;t just use any TTS as some of them once put through the RVC turned out really weird. After some time I stumbled upon the TTS service called &lt;a href=&#34;https://ttsfree.com/text-to-speech&#34;&gt;TTSFree&lt;/a&gt; which, despite it&amp;rsquo;s discouraging name, had a large range of TTS voice&amp;rsquo;s from Google and Microsoft. The website also allowed manipulation of speed and pitch. And thus the text document &lt;code&gt;how to - pp&lt;/code&gt; was formed. It detailed the exact instructions on how to create the perfect Mr P vocie. Since then I recreated some of Mr P&amp;rsquo;s famous lines that I mentioned earlier. Mr P still doesn&amp;rsquo;t know that I&amp;rsquo;ve done this, and I don&amp;rsquo;t know if I want to tell him since I don&amp;rsquo;t know how he&amp;rsquo;ll react, I don&amp;rsquo;t exactly want to get expelled or suspended you know.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Anyways that&amp;rsquo;s it for now, sorry for not providing examples of the voice clone, didn&amp;rsquo;t think it was too appropiate to being sharing my teachers voice around online. Hopefully the next post won&amp;rsquo;t be another month but I&amp;rsquo;m not sure. Bye!&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First post</title>
      <link>https://itxweird.github.io/posts/first_post/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2023 08:18:14 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://itxweird.github.io/posts/first_post/</guid>
      <description>Hello there Hi everyone, this will be my first post on this blog, and first post using hugo, I&amp;rsquo;m really terrible at hugo, cause well&amp;hellip; uhhh&amp;hellip;
Yeah&amp;hellip; But it&amp;rsquo;s working now which is all that matters.
I hope to post a decent bit, my first proper post will be about how I made an AI voice for one of my teachers, it&amp;rsquo;s a good story.
Anyways, that&amp;rsquo;s it for now, see you in the next post!</description>
      <content>&lt;h1 id=&#34;hello-there&#34;&gt;Hello there&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hi everyone, this will be my first post on this blog, and first post using hugo, I&amp;rsquo;m really terrible at hugo, cause well&amp;hellip; uhhh&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;workflows.png&#34; alt=&#34;losts of workflows&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Yeah&amp;hellip; But it&amp;rsquo;s working now which is all that matters.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I hope to post a decent bit, my first &lt;em&gt;proper&lt;/em&gt; post will be about how I made an AI voice for one of my teachers, it&amp;rsquo;s a good story.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Anyways, that&amp;rsquo;s it for now, see you in the next post!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;edit&#34;&gt;Edit:&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I decided to delete the old repository and replace it with a new one, I was too embarassed at how many times it took me to actually get my website working, and it looks really weird with some bright green dot on my contributions thingy saying 35 commits on a singular day, all for this damn blog lol.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://itxweird.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://itxweird.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>About Hiya! I&amp;rsquo;m Weird, otherwise known as weird6001 or ItxWeird
I&amp;rsquo;m a highschool student currently in year 10
This blog is bascially where I&amp;rsquo;m going put documentation of journaling of random projects that I have, hope you enjoy!
If you&amp;rsquo;re looking to contact me, please see here.</description>
      <content>&lt;h1 id=&#34;about&#34;&gt;About&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hiya! I&amp;rsquo;m Weird, otherwise known as weird6001 or ItxWeird&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m a highschool student currently in year 10&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This blog is bascially where I&amp;rsquo;m going put documentation of journaling of random projects that I have, hope you enjoy!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you&amp;rsquo;re looking to contact me, please see &lt;a href=&#34;https://itxweird.github.io/contact/&#34;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://itxweird.github.io/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://itxweird.github.io/contact/</guid>
      <description>Contact I&amp;rsquo;m usually pretty acitve on these platforms, so I should reply decently fast
Discord: weird6001
Twitter(X): @dingofhud
Email: hudsonding405@gmail.com
GitHub: github.com/ItxWeird
If for whatever reason I don&amp;rsquo;t respond, I&amp;rsquo;m probably busy or away doing something else</description>
      <content>&lt;h1 id=&#34;contact&#34;&gt;Contact&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m usually pretty acitve on these platforms, so I should reply decently fast&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Discord&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;code&gt;weird6001&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Twitter(X)&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/dingofhud&#34;&gt;&lt;code&gt;@dingofhud&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Email&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;code&gt;hudsonding405@gmail.com&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;GitHub&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/ItxWeird&#34;&gt;&lt;code&gt;github.com/ItxWeird&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If for whatever reason I don&amp;rsquo;t respond, I&amp;rsquo;m probably busy or away doing something else&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
